(Bert:)I'm warning you,
(Bert:)hide your good rocks.
(Mrs Petrescu:)My sister's husband
took all her things, too.
Story at 11:00.
(Stuart:)Really, no one else is coming?
Oh, this is it.
(Sheldon:)You are the practice round.
(Stuart:)Practice round? For-for what?
(Amy:)Uh, no.
He-he just means that
(Amy:)you were the first people
we thought of.
(Sheldon:)You know, exactly.
(Sheldon:)We've never thrown
a brunch before,
(Sheldon:)and I wanted to work
out all the kinks.
(Stuart:)So, I'm like a lab rat
(Stuart:)before your real friends
come over?
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)You see, your words
sound reasonable,
(Sheldon:)but your face
looks angry.
(Sheldon:)Help me out here.
This is not where I shine.
(Sheldon:)Stuart,
(Amy:)you know you're one of
our favorite people.
(Sheldon:)Okay, now, see,
you look sincere,
(Sheldon:)but your words are
completely false.
(Sheldon:)I'm glad we did
this test run.
(Sheldon:)These brunches
are wild!